Guide to the Charles F. Bates Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 3; (5 boxes)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS AND ILLUSTRATIONS
    - Custer Family
      - Custer, George Armstrong: Portraits, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 431)
    - Group Poses
      - Indians at Pine Ridge Indian Agency, Fort Niobrara, Nebraska, ca. 1902 (Box 26, Folder 432)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS AND ILLUSTRATIONS
    - Battle Images
      - [Civil War], 1861 (Box 26, Folder 433)
      - "Custer's Demand" painting by Charles Schreyvogel (Box 26, Folder 434)
      - [Custer's Last Stand] painting by James E. Taylor (Box 26, Folder 435)
      - "Discovery of Men of the Kidder Party" painting by J. E. Taylor, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 436)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Unidentified place, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 437)
  - RESEARCH FILES
    - Edward S. Godfrey
      - Official Papers: Seventh Cavalry records, 1874, 1876 (Box 27, Folder 438)
    - Marcus Reno
      - 1879 Investigation: Contemporary newspaper accounts: 1879 Jan-Mar, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 439)
    - Nineteenth-Century Army-Indian Campaigns
      - 1868 Campaign: Contemporary newspaper accounts: 1868-69, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 440)
      - 1875 Campaign: Contemporary newspaper accounts: 1875, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 441)
      - 1876 Campaign: Contemporary newspaper accounts: 1876, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 442-43)
      - 1876 Campaign: Histories: 1886-1947, n.d., 1900-47, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 444)
      - Indians: Histories: 1868 (Box 28, Folder 445)
    - Custer Monument and 20th Century Observances
      - Newspaper Clippings: 1932, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 446)
  - BACKGROUND MATERIAL
    - American West
      - Histories: Winners of the West newspaper series 1926-36 (Box 28, Folder 447-50)
      - Histories: Winners of the West newspaper series 1937-39 (Box 29, Folder 451-52)
      - Belknap, William W., n.d. (Box 29, Folder 453)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS AND ILLUSTRATIONS
    - Places and Monuments
      - Fort Riley, Kansas, 1906 (Box 30, Folder 454-55)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 456)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 1.75; (1 box)
  Box 31, Restricted Fragile Papers, contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 4, folder 33 (Box 31, Folder 457)
  - Box 15, folder 204 (Box 31, Folder 458)
  - Box 19, folder 276 (Box 31, Folder 459)